

🛮 (+91) 8788223475 | 🗷 nikirar97@gmail.com | 😭 nekomyst.com | 🖸 Nekomyst | 🛅 iam-nikita | 💆 @Nekomyst

# **Summary**

Current Security Engineer at a food delivery and restaurant discovery company, Zomato. 2+ years experience specializing in Security Engineering, Security Automation, Penetration Testing, Threat Modeling, Application Security Reviews, Code Review, DevSecOps and BugBounty Program Management. Interested in tackling Security challenges that a thriving and fast paced SDLC brings, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

# **Work Experience**

Zomato India

SECURITY ENGINEER Jun 2021 - Present

- Securing Zomato's SDLC by incorporating security at each step of the SDLC.
- Perform Application Security Reviews for internal security testing of Zomato products.
- · Security Automation and Tooling to support infrastructure monitoring and alerting the security issues found.
- Built and maintaining the SAST environment in Zomato's Secure SDLC.
- Designing and Incorporating the Threat Modeling roadmap in the current SDLC at Zomato.
- Continuous VAPT, Code Reviews, Threat Modeling, DevSecOps practices and Asset Monitoring.
- Developer Security Education Trainings, Quiz Sessions, Emailers, Security Checklist, Security News-letter.
- Manage Zomato's Bug Bounty Program.

Impact Analytics Indic

SECURITY SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Jul 2020 - Jun 202.

- Designed, developed and implemented Secure Authentication Layer (Firebase, Google Identity Platform), Platform Access Control, Granular Roles and Permissions, and User Lifecycle for User Management.
- Implemented Repudiation Mitigation Persistent and Immutable Logging
- Developed and maintained backend Django codebases for the major components of Core Product platform.

 AppSecure
 India

 Security Engineer Intern
 Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

Performed VAPT by assessing web application's Infrastructure design and Business logic to discover high impact flaws and threats in the application.

- Extensive Manual and Automated Security assessment of various applications with vast technology stack (Node.js, Express, RESTful APIs, PHP, Django, React, Ruby on Rails, GraphQL etc.) and hacking them to discover high impact bugs.
- Black-Box security assessments with detailed advisory reports regarding all the findings and recommendation for their mitigation.

#### Outreachy (inspired by GSoC)

Remote

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN @ F# SOFTWARE FOUNDATION

May 2019 - Aug 2019

• Created FsAutocomplete support for .NET Template Engine ('dotnet new') with the required unit tests and integration tests for production level support code in FsAutocomplete software.

### Skills\_

**Security** Web Security • API Security • DevSecOps • Threat Modeling • Code Review • Penetration-Testing • CTFs • BugHunting

**DevSecOps** SAST • DAST • Secure CI/CD

**Programming** Python • Django • JavaScript • Node-JS • PHP • MySQL • C • C++ • Algorithms • Data Structures • Web Development

**Tools & Frameworks** Burp Suite • Nuclei • Prisma Cloud (Palo Alto) • Express • Django • Git

### **Education**

#### National Institute of Technology, Goa (NIT Goa)

Goa, India

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

Jun 2016 - Jun 2020

• CGPA: 8.07/10

 MajorCourses: NetworkSecurity, Cryptography, Data Structure and Algorithms, Computer Networks, Operating Systems, Database Systems, Object Oriented Programming.

APRIL 25, 2022 NIKITA · RÉSUMÉ 1

### Navy Children School, Goa (NCS Goa)

Goa, India

12th and 10th Grade

HIGH SCHOOL - ALL INDIA SENIOR SCHOOL CERTIFICATE EXAMINATION

XII Grade: 88.60%X Grade: 9.60/10

## (II Grade: 88.60%

# Other\_

#### **PROJECTS**

• MONTAGE - Montage is a Recon Automation Framework built for Asset Reconnaissance and Enumeration. Built using NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, Elastic Search, Minio

#### **CTFs**

• DiceCTF 2021 • ShaktiCTF 2021 • BSides Delhi CTF • DamCTF • TokyoWesterns CTF 2020 • HactivityCon CTF • BSides Ahmedabad BatPwn 2020 • NullCon Winja 2020 • PicoCTF 2019 • Women Unite Over CTF 2019

# **OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS**

• OWASP Juice-Shop • F# Software Foundation